Shamira Stone

6545 Green Valley Cir unit 303 Culver City, CA 90230

SUMMARY

A highly motivated individual with great interpersonal and communication skills, possess strong skills, strategic thinker and team builder with experience working in both small and large corporate environment. Looks for opportunities to grow and takes initiative to meet overall operational goals.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2016-Current

Phone: (323) 381 9888 [Cell]

Email: shamirazetina@gmail.com

One Main Financial

Sr Personal Loan Specialist

Currently working as a Sr Loan Processor/Assistant manager assisting customers with Title loan, auto refinancing and signature loans.

Responsibilities Includes:

- -Collecting on past due Accounts;
- -Collecting and processing payments Via Cash, Check, and Debit;
- -Managing and running office when manager is out;
- -Loan underwriting approving and Declining loans;
- -Processing bank deposits;
- -Daily balancing of drawer;

Dollar Loan Center 2015-2016

Loan Processor

Worked as a loan processor; assisted customers with Title Loans and Signature Loans.

Responsibilities Included:

- -Collecting and processing Payments Via Cash and Credit cards;
- Daily check and balance of Drawer and Vault;
- -Maintain accurate and effective filing records;
- -Provide excellent customer service;
- -Perform additional office duties:

PLS Financial Services 2014-2015

<u>Customer Service Representative</u>

Worked as a CSR; assisted customer with check cashing and other office responsibilities.

Responsibilities Included:

- -Cash Handling
- -Check Cashing;
- -International Wire transfers;
- -Cross-selling services/merchandise;
- -Daily balancing of sales and reports;
- -Excellent customer service;
- -Collecting and processing payments via Cash and Credit cards;

Ranch Market 2012 -2014

Supervisor/Cashier

Worked as a cashier attendant with additional office responsibilities assigned.

Responsibilities included:

- -Operating cash registers, collecting and processing payments via cash and credit cards;
- -Assist customers during checkout;
- -Process money orders and money grams;
- -Process billings and payments for business;
- -Assist floor managers and Cashier
- -Daily check and balance of day's sales, including voiding checks, cashing checks, producing end of day's sale reports.

EDUCATION

Sacred Heart Junior College - Cayo, Belize 2011

Certificate in Tourism Management

Saint Ignatius High School - Cayo, Belize 2009

High School Diploma with concentration in Business Studies